Guide to Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art special events records, 1891-2010 COR0003.4.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Dailies, Circa 1985 - 2010; Series 13
  - Dailies, 1989 September; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 4; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 6; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 7; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 8; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 9; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 10; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 11; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 12; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 14; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 15; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 17; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 18; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 20; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 22; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 23; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 24; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 25; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 26; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 27; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 29; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Dailies, 1989 September 30; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Dailies, 1989 October; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 1; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 2; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 3; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 4; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 5; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 6; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 7; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 11; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 12; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 13; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 14; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 15; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 16; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 17; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 18; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 19; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 21; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 22; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 23; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 24; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 26; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 25; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 27; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Dailies, 1988 October 28; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 30; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Dailies, 1989 October 31; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Dailies, 1989 November; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 2; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 3; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 4; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 5; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 6; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 9; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 10; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 11; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 12; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 13; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 16; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 18; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 20; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Dailies, 1989 Novemebr 25; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Dailies, 1989 Novemebr 27; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 28; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 29; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Dailies, 1989 November 30; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Dailies, 1989 December; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Dailies, 1989 December 1; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Dailies, 1989 December 2; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Dailies, 1989 December 4; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Dailies, 1989 December 5; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Dailies, 1989 Decemebr 6; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Dailies, 1989 December 7; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Dailies, 1989 December 9; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Dailies, 1989 December 10; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Dailies, 1989 December 11; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Dailies, 1989 Decemebr 13; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Dailies, 1989 December 15; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Dailies, 1989 December 18; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - June 1990 Correspondence, 1990 June; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - May 1990 Correspondence, 1990 May; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - April 1990 Correspondence, 1990 April; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - March 1990 Correspondence, 1990 March; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Dailies, 1990 February; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Correpondence, 1990 January; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Correpondence, 1989 February; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 88)
  - Correpondence, 1989 January; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 89)
  - Correpondence, 1989 December; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 90)
  - Correpondence, 1989 November; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 91)
  - Correpondence, 1989 October; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 92)
  - Correpondence, 1989 September; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 93)
  - Correpondence, 1989 August; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Correpondence, 1989 July; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Correpondence, 1989 June; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Correpondence, 1989 May; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Correpondence, 1989 April; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Correpondence, 1989 March; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Correpondence, 1988 November; Series 13 (Box 6, Folder 100)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 5; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 6; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 9; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 10; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 13; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 10-15; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 14; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 16; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 17; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 18; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 19; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 20; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 21; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 23; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 24; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 25; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 26; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 27; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 28; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 29; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 30; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Dailes, 1989 January 31; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 3; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 6; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 8; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 9; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 10; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 11; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 13; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 15; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 17; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 18; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 19; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 22; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 23; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 24; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 25; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 26; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 27; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Dailes, 1989 February 28; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 1; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 2; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 3; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 4; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 5; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 6; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 7; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 8; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 9; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 11; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 12; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 13; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 16; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 17; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 18; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 19; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 23; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 25; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 26; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 27; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 28; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 29; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Dailes, 1989 March 30; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 3; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 4; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 5; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 6; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 8; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 9; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 10; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 11; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 12; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 13; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 14; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 15; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 16; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 17; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 18; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 20; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 23; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 24; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 25; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 26; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Dailes, 1989 April 30; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Dailes, 1989 May; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 1; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 2; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 3; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 4; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 5; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 6; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 7; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 8; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 9; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 11; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 12; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 13; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 14; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 15; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 16; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 18; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 19; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 20; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 21; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 22; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 23; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 25; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 26; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Dailes, 1989 May 30; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 2; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 3; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 4; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 5; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 6; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 7; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 10; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 11; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 12; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 13; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 15; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 16; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 17; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 19; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 22; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 23; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 24; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 26; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 27; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 28; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Dailes, 1989 June 29; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Robert Mapplethorpe Membership Preview Reception, 1989 June 30; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Dailes, 1989 July; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Dailes, 1989 July 9; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Dailes, 1989 July 13; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Dailes, 1989 July 15; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Dailes, 1989 July 17; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Dailes, 1989 July 20; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Dailes, 1989 July 25; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Dailes, 1989 July 29; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Dailes, 1989 August; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Dailes, 1989 August 3; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Dailes, 1989 August 6; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Dailes, 1989 August 10; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Dailes, 1989 August 17; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Dailes, 1989 August 29; Series 13 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 31; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 30; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 28; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 23; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 24; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 22; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 20; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 19; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 18; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 17; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 15; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 14; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 13; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 12; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 11; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 9; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 6; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 2; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 4; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Dailies, 1991 May 1; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Dailies, 1991 May; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 30; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 29; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 28; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 24; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 22; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 21; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 18; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 17; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 16; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 12; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 11; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 10; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 7; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 6; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 4; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 3; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Dailies, 1991 April 1; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Dailies, 1991 April; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 26; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 25; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 24; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 21; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 20; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 19; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 15; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 14; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Dailies (Empty), 1991 March 10; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 8; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 7; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 6; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 5; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 4; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Dailies, 1991 March 2; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Dailies, 1991 March; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Dailies, 1991 February 28; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Dailies (Empty), 1991 February 27; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Dailies, 1991 February 26; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Dailies, 1991 February 25; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Dailies, 1991 February 23; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Dailies, 1991 February 22; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Dailies, 1991 February 21; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Dailies, 1991 February 20; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Dailies, 1991 February 13; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Dailies, 1991 February 12; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Dailies, 1991 February 9; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Dailies, 1991 February 7; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Dailies, 1991 February 6; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Dailies, 1991 February 5; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Dailies, 1991 February; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 30; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 29; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 28; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 25; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Dailies, 19911 January 24; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 23; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 22; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 19; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 15; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 14; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 12; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 11; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 10; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 9; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Dailies, 1991 January 3; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Dailies, 1991 January; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Events 1991, Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 18; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 17; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 15; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 14; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - Dailies, 1990 Decemebr 13; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 12; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 93)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 11; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 94)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 9; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 95)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 10; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 96)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 8; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 7; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 6; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 5; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 3; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 2; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Dailies, 1990 December 1; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Dailies, 1990 December; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 30; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 29; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 28; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 27; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 26; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 109)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 24; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 110)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 19; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 111)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 18; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 112)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 17; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 113)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 14; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 114)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 12; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 115)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 9; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 116)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 7; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 117)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 6; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 118)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 5; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 119)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 4; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 120)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 3; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 121)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 2; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 122)
  - Dailies, 1990 November 1; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 123)
  - Dailies, 1990 November; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 124)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 31; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 125)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 30; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 126)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 29; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 127)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 28; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 128)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 27; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 129)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 26; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 130)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 25; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 131)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 24; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 132)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 23; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 133)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 22; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 21; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 20; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 136)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 19; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 137)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 17; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 138)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 16; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 139)
  - Am. Stock Exchange, 1990 October 15; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 140)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 14; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 141)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 13; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 142)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 11; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 143)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 10; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 4; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 3; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 146)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 2; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 147)
  - Dailies, 1990 October 1; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Dailies, 1990 October; Series 13 (Box 8, Folder 149)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 30; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 29; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 28; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 27; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 26; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 25; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 23; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 22; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 21; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 20; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 19; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 17; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 16; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Dailies, 1990 September 11; Series 13 (Box 9, Folder 14)